Sukhdit Saini

49 Sal Circle Brampton, ON, L6R +1 (437)-248-4601 sukhditsaini@gmail.com

EDUCATION

Sep 2020 - York University - Toronto

Present Currently studying Bachelor of Arts in Information Technology.

Sep 2016 - St. Marguerite D'Youville Secondary School

Jun 2020 High School Diploma

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Jan 2022 -July 2022

Food Service Worker, New York Fries - Vaughan, ON

- Maintained clean, trash-free workspaces to maximize productivity and safety.
- Developed and maintained positive relationships with customers to enhance service.
- Strictly followed sanitation and food safety guidelines as required by regulatory agencies and company.
- Prepared and served various food and drink items to customer specifications in fast-paced environments.
- Restocked supplies and prepared additional ingredients during downtime for expected busy periods.
- Learned other teammates' work tasks to train as backup.

May 2019 -Jan 2020

Dishwasher (volunteer), Sri Guru Nanak Sikh Centre - Brampton, ON

- Kept kitchen areas neat and clean by removing trash and organizing supplies
- Cleared, washed and stacked all plates, dining utensils, and trays quickly and without breaking.
- Followed supervisor instructions to complete tasks on time.
- Kept dishes, utensils and glassware clean and rotated following safety standards set by restaurant.
- Assisted with kitchen prep work to help operations run smoothly and meet customer needs.
- Kept work area clean, dry, and free of debris to prevent incidents and accidents.
- Worked with chemicals such as detergent, rinse agents, and sanitizers to protect customer health.
- Washed equipment, surfaces, refrigerators, and other areas and applied sanitizing chemicals.

Dec 2020 -Present

Snow Shoveler, Independently Employed - Brampton ON

- Completed prompt snow removal process during and after weather events.
- Applied salt or chemical solutions to surfaces as preventive measure against snow and ice buildup.
- Maintained clean, orderly work environment free of hazards.
- Upheld safety standards for working in wet, cold and windy conditions.

SKILLS & EXPERTISE

- Flexibility
- Physical strength
- Stress management
- Task prioritization
- Hand-eye coordination
- Snow shoveling technique
- Programming Languages
- Python Programming Language
- Java Programming Language
- Software Design

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Skilled multitasker with superior work ethic and good teamwork, problem-solving and organizational skills. Willing to take on any task to help the team. Reliable and dedicated team player with a hardworking and resourceful approach. Effective Student committed to learning, developing skills in programming languages and team contribution. Self-directed and energetic with superior performance in both autonomous or collaborative environments working independently and collaborating with others on group projects. Experienced in multiple programming languages such as Java, Python, and MATLAB.